Guide to the Morris State Bank (Pony, Montana) Records 1899-1927
Montana Historical Society Archives
Morris State Bank (Pony, Montana) Records
1899-1927
Montana Historical Society, Research Center Archives 225 N. Roberts PO Box 201201 Helena MT 59620-1201 (406) 444-4774 mhslibrary@mt.gov
MC 175
Morris State Bank (Pony, Mont.)
3.5 linear feet of shelf space
The Morris State Bank was located in Pony, Montana. Records (1899-1927) include correspondence concerning the Pony Electric Light Company, Elling and Morris, Morris and Flint, Citizen's Telephone Company, Montana Tonopah Mining Company, Hennepin Ore Company, and others; court papers; financial records; legal documents; subject files concerning the Citizens' Telephone Company, Elling and Morris, and the Indian Gold Mining Company; and miscellany. There are subgroups for Morris and Flint and for Fred G. Smith.
The Morris State Bank was opened in Pony, Montana, in 1902, with a capital stock of $50,000. The bank moved into a newly constructed building in early 1903. William W. Morris was president of the Morris State Bank until his death in October 19O4. Thomas Duncan served initially as vice president and then succeeded to the presidency in 1905. Following his death that same year, Mary B. Elling became president. Charles E. Morris served as a director in 19O2 and became vice president in 1905. Cashiers for the bank included Philip H. (Harry) Gohn and Fred G. Smith. Other officers included M. M. Duncan, a Virginia City attorney, who served as a director, and Henry J. Schreiber who was a vice president beginning in 1904. By June 1906, the Morris State Bank had achieved deposits in the amount of $200,000 and was conducting business with banks in Montana and throughout the country. A close business relationship existed with the Elling State Bank of Virginia City and the Union Bank and Trust Company of Helena, whose president was George L. Ramsey. The Montana banks were members of the Montana Bankers Association which issued warnings about fraudulent customers in the state and informed banks of pending legislation effecting the banking industry in the state. The officers and directors of the Morris State Bank were businessmen and active members of the Pony community. Several businesses were connected to the bank through these people. Henry Elling and William Morris were partners in Elling and Morris, which had a quartz mill and an electric light plant. Charles E. Morris and James A. Flint, an attorney, were partners in Morris and Flint, a real estate and insurance business, with an office in the Morris State Bank building. Harry Gohn was president of Citizens Telephone Company. Fred Smith was a notary, trustee for the board of education, an insurance agent, and mayor of Pony in 1911. Henry Schreiber ran a mercantile company and served as treasurer for the city. The Morris State Bank closed and went into voluntary liquidation on February 1, 1926. At that time the board of directors borrowed $96,000 from the Elling Estates Company so that all depositors could be paid. The bank then came under the jurisdiction of a liquidating agent.
Content Description:
This collection contains primarily of incoming correspondence (1902-1909) and general correspondence (1910-1917) of P.H. "Harry" Gohn and Fred G. Smith, cashiers of the Morris State Bank. This correspondence includes routine bank business as well as correspondence relating to other businesses and investments in which the bank's officers and directors were involved (Pony Electric Light Company, Elling and Morris, Morris and Flint, Citizens Telephone Company, Montana-Tonopah Mining Company, Hennepin Ore Company, and others). Other materials in the collection include court papers (1907-1916); financial records (1902-1917) including assessments, registers of daily statements and drafts, journals, daily balances, reports of condition, and tax statements; legal documents (1902-1913) including agreements, deeds, licenses, and notices of protest; subject files (1908-1917) for other businesses (including the Citizens Telephone Company, Elling and Morris, and the Indian Gold Mining Company); and miscellany (advertisements, insurance policies, sample forms, letterhead, etc.). There is a subgroup for Morris and Flint (1887-1927) which includes information on the insurance business, descriptions of local buildings being insured, and prospecti for several mining companies including Black Pine Mining Company (Butte), Dailey Group of claims (Jefferson County), Leviathan Gold Mining Company (Madison County), Rocky Mountain Exploration Company, and Stockton Copper Mining Company (Broadwater County). A subgroup for Fred G. Smith (1906-1916) concerns his insurance business.
Arrangement:
by subgroup and series
Acquisition Information:
available upon request
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society Archives catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Banks and banking--Montana--Pony; Gold mines and mining--Montana--Pony; Insurance companies--Montana--Pony; Mines and mineral resources--Montana--Madison County; Telephone companies-- Montana--Pony; Helena (Mont.)--Commerce; Pony (Mont.)--Commerce; Virginia City (Mont.)--Commerce; Montana; Business, Industry, and Labor
Detailed Description of the Collection
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection
- Morris State Bank
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - W. Henry Adkins and E.S. Adkins, 1903-1906, 1908 (Box-folder 1 / 1)
    - American Bankers Association, 1902-1908 (Box-folder 1 / 2)
    - American Smelting and Refining Company, 1904-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 3)
    - Anaconda Copper Mining Company, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 4)
    - A (correspondents include Abbott Alkaloidal Company, Anna Adams Estate, W.H. Adams, J. Albright, W.J. Albro, Walter Alderson, Allen and Gilbert-Ramaker Company, Thomas Allen, Allis-Chalmers Company, American Harrow Company, American National Bank of Helena, American National Bank of San Francisco, American Surety Company, Charlie Armstrong, E.R. Avery, Dudley F. Ayres), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 5)
    - Clara E. Barclay and J.R. Barclay, 1905-1908 (Box-folder 1 / 6)
    - Brown, Treacy and Sperry Company, 1905-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 7)
    - Butte Adjustment Company; Butte and Willow Creek Mining Company; Butte Commercial Bank; Butte Electric Supply Company; Butte Potato and Produce Company; Butte-Potosi Mining Company, 1906-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 8)
    - B (correspondents include M.I. Baker, E.L. Ballou, Bankers Life Association, Barker and Wilson, Albert Barter, George Bauerman, Edwin S. Beall, W.H. Beall, John Berkin, Blackhawk Mining Company, Mrs. Henry N. Blake, Judah Boas Company, W.N. Bowman, Box family, Charlie Boyd, Bradstreet Company, E.M. Brooke, Bryant Supply Company, S.R. Buford and Company, Robert E. Burns, Burroughs Adding Machine Company, E.C. Bush), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 9)
    - Carbon County Bank, 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 10)
    - Clark and Duncan (W.A. Clark and M.M. Duncan), 1906-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 11)
    - W.A. Clark [William Alexander Clark] (includes Clark and Duncan law firm, Elling State Bank), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 12)
    - W.A. Clark and Brother bank [William Andrews Clark], 1904-1908 (Box-folder 1 / 13)
    - Commercial National Bank (Bozeman; Chicago), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 14)
    - C (correspondents include Edmund J. Callaway, Lew L. Callaway, M. Canby, Alice Carruthers, J.E. Chambers, O.P. Chisholm, Citizens' Telephone Company, Bert Clark, C.L. Clark, Philo M. Clark, J.Z. Clem, J.M. Cline, Colliers National Weekly, Columbus Mercantile Company, Raymond Conard, John S. Cook and Company, Cootey-Blodgett Company, R.T. Courtney, S.U. Cox, W.P. Curteman), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 15)
    - Daly Bank and Trust Company, 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 16)
    - M.M. Duncan (see also: Clark and Duncan), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 17)
    - D (correspondents include E.C. Davis, H.E. Day, F.B. Dickerson, C.A. Dillet, Charles O. Dorr, John N. Dryer, Paul S. Duncan), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 18)
    - Elling State Bank (includes Thomas Duncan, W.A. Clark, Clyde Morris), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 19)
    - E (correspondents include Economy Ink Company, Louisa Eldredge, Mary B. Elling, Elizabeth H. Ellis, James Ellison, Ely Salyards and Company, W.J. Ennis, Eschle Plumbing and Heating Company, Everybody's Meat Company), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 20)
    - First National Bank (Butte; Freeland PA; Kalispell; Lanark IL; Staples MN; Meteetsee WY; Youngstown OH), 1903-1908 (Box-folder 1 / 21)
    - First National Bank of San Francisco, 1903-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 22)
    - James A. Flint, 1903-1908 (Box-folder 1 / 23)
    - French and Powell (Virginia City Post Office), 1902-1903 (Box-folder 1 / 24)
    - F (correspondents include Farmers State Bank, Thomas A. Ferguson, F.M. Field, J.J. Finch, Mae Finch, First State Bank Livingston, Forbis and Mattison, E.C. Frisbee, C.L. Friedericks, Fruitland Farms Company), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 25)
    - P.H. "Harry" Gohn and Virginia Gohn, 1906-1909 (Box-folder 1 / 26)
    - G (correspondents include Galen and Mettler, Gallatin Valley Milling Company, Garnet Gold Mining Company, E.H. Gay and Company, W.H. Geer, Sol Genzberger, Goldfield Consolidated Mines Company, Goldfield Investment Company, Goodyear Rubber Company, Gurney Gordon, A.C. Gormley, C.H. Green, C.F. Gregory), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 1)
    - C.H. Hand, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 2)
    - L.F. Hare, 1906-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 3)
    - Hennepin Ore Company, 1902-1903 (Box-folder 2 / 4)
    - L.O. Hickok and Son, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 5)
    - H (correspondents include E.C. Hackley, George B. Hadzor, J.E. Hale, K.W. Hale, Hancock Brothers, E.M. Hanzlik, Charles D. Harper, Harper and MacDonald, Fayette Harrington, Harrison Ranch, Mrs. H.C. Harrison, Hartman and Hartman, Hawkeye Elevator Company, R.N. Hawkins, P.N. Haycraft, H.S. Hepner, E.A. Higinbotham, Samuel Holman, Hongkong and Shanghai Banking Corporation, W.R. Hubbard and Company, Clifton W. Hudson, T.B. Hunt, S.E. Hunter, Thomas G. Hutt), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 6)
    - Indian Gold Mining Company, 1904-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 7)
    - I (correspondents include Idaho Smelting and Refining Company, J.E. Irvine, E.W. Jack, C.S. Jackman Company, Gus Janney, Fred S. Johnson, John Johnson, Albert Jones, James E. Jones, Jones Fruit Company), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 8)
    - Roger C. Knox (includes Montana Revenue Gold Mining Company), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 9)
    - K (correspondents include Kenkel-Todd Company, John N. Kirk, Joseph Kirschwing, Bessie A. Kneedler, C.G. Kohl, Kountze Brothers, Alfred S. Kyle), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 10)
    - Levey Brothers and Company, 1903-1908 (Box-folder 2 / 11)
    - A.W. Lignell (German and Lignell, Architects), 1903 (Box-folder 2 / 12)
    - Walter F. Lord, 1904-1908 (Box-folder 2 / 13)
    - L (correspondents include Lafayette Bank, Larson and Greenough, James Leffell, George and Emma Leunstrend, J.H. Levy, George L. Lewis, John P. Lewis, Charles Leyendecker, W.W. Livingston, R.A. Luke and Company), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 14)
    - Madison County government (includes W.A. Stevenson, C.E. Reese, J.Z. Clem, C.H. Buford, George E. Gohn, R.N. Hawkins), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 15)
    - John C. Mahoney (includes P.J. Leonard Estate), 1906-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 16)
    - Ma-Mc (correspondents include Alexander Mackel; Joe Mackel; W.D. Manley; Sam Marshall; Lee Martin; Fred Maryott; Marysville [Wash.] State Bank; Seward Mason; Charles Mattison; Mabel Alkine May; Mayo Feed Company; Mayo, Sachs and Company; James A. McAllister; McCabe Brothers; Mrs. D.O. McClanahan; McCormick and Company, Bankers; McCurdy and Haycroft; Jessie McDonald; W.C. McKaskle; Mrs. C.V. McVey), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 17-18)
    - Me-Mi (correspondents include George Meldrum and Company, Samuel A. Mendenhall, F.R. Merk, Frank W. Mettler, C.L. Meyer, Michigan Buggy Company, Michigan Leather Company, John Mikesell, Mary L. Miller, Frank D. Miracle, Mississippi Valley Trust Company), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 19)
    - Montana Bankers Association, 1905-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 20)
    - Montana State Examiner, 1905-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 21)
    - Montana Tonopah Mining Company, 1902-1907 (Box-folder 2 / 22)
    - Montana Treasurer's Office, 1905-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 23)
    - Montana state government (includes Montana Agricultural Experiment Station; Montana Bureau of Agriculture, Labor and Industry; Montana Auditor's Office; Montana Secretary of State; Montana State Land Department), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 24)
    - Montana companies and organizations (includes Montana Record Publishing Company; Montana Development League; Montana Electric Company; Montana Farmers' Institutes; Montana Hardware Company; Montana-Hecla Mining Company; Montana Nevada Mining Company; Montana Wool Growers Commission Company), 1906-1908 (Box-folder 2 / 25)
    - Morris family (includes Charles E. Morris, C.R. Morris, Fred Morris, Leah Morris, W.C. Morris, W.W. Morris), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 26-27)
    - Mo-My (correspondents include Fred Moore, Mrs. Price Moorhead, J.R. Morrisey, Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, Frank C. Myers), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 28)
    - National Bank of Commerce in New York, 1902-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 29)
    - C.E. Noble, 1904-1906 (Box-folder 2 / 30)
    - Norris Mercantile Company (includes J.R. Whitmore), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 2 / 31)
    - Northern Pacific Railway Company; Northern Pacific Express Company, 1903-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 1)
    - John Northey, 1905-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 2)
    - N-O (correspondents include National Bank of California, National Bank of Commerce in St. Louis, National Bank of Gallatin Valley, National Bank of the Republic, National Mining and Investment Company, National Shoe and Leather Bank, National Surety Company, James Naughton, Nevada Smelting and Mines Company, New York National Exchange Bank, Samuel Newhouse, Lillian Nord, Northern Hotel Register Company, Northwestern National Bank, Northwestern Improvement Company, Chong On, Orton Bothers, J.H. Owen), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 3)
    - J.M. Pile, 1904-1908 (Box-folder 3 / 4)
    - P (correspondents include Ike Pace, H. Pagnuelo, J.H. Pankey, Webb Parkison Estate, Charles C. Parsons, J.H. Patrick, W.O. Peck, Gust A. Petrick, W.G. Pfouts, Rhoda Pierce, C.D. Pinckney, Harry T. Poindexter, H.F. Poland, R.L. Polk and Company, James A. Pollock and Company, Goerge H. Potter, A.S. Pratt and Sons, Proctor Knott Gold Mining Company, Publishers Clearing House, C.A. Purdom), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 5)
    - Anna Richter, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 6)
    - R (correspondents include John C. Ramsey, The Rand Company, Raven Mining Company, Raymond Commercial Club, Winthrop Raymond, James W. Rea and Company, T.B. Reagan, D.N. Reber, Red Bluff Gold Mining Company, Red Top Mining Company of Goldfield, J.W. Reed, W.A. Reel, A. Ira Renick, Republican National Committee, Joseph E. Richards, W. Richtmyer, Nick Rider, J.A. Rightenour, James G. Roberts, Thomas S. Robinson and Company, Rocky Fork Coal Company, Rocky Mountain Bell Telephone Company, H.E. Rooks, Paul R. Rosin, Fred Rowlands, E.L. Ruegamer), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 7)
    - W.H. Schamp, 1906-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 8)
    - O.Y. Schulenburg, 1903-1906 (Box-folder 3 / 9)
    - C. Al Shay (re several mining companies), 1904-1907 (Box-folder 3 / 10)
    - William Simpson, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 3 / 11)
    - Smith (includes Charles M. Smith, Mrs. E.L. Smith, E.M. Smith, Frank Smith, H.F. Smith, Joseph Smith, R.T. Smith), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 12)
    - S.V. Stewart, 1905-1908 (Box-folder 3 / 13)
    - Joseph M. Stoker; John H. Stoker, 1903-1908 (Box-folder 3 / 14)
    - S (correspondents include Allen C. Sanders, Lester Sanford, H.H. Sappington, Albert Saylor, J.M. Scanland, Lewis F. Scheytt, Helen Schmuck, H.J. Schreiner, Seattle Clearing House Association, Seattle National Bank, W.A. Shea, Daniel S. Shenk, W. Shields, Walter Shobe, C.S. Shoemaker, Z.A. Short, Joe Sicard, Silver Bow National Bank, Charles A. Spirk, H.J. Springer, John Standake, Standard Publishing Company, George H. Stanton, State Bank and Trust Company [Tonopah, Nev.], State Bank of Dillon, H.E. Steffins, Steurer Publishing Company, Andrew Stewart, William Stinson, Fred H. Stock, Stoller Live Stock Commission Company, M.W. Stout, J.H. Stovel, C.R. Stranahan, H.T. Strollwood, Silas Stuart, Stumpf and Hay), 1903-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 15)
    - A.W. and C.E. Tanner, 1904-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 16)
    - Tinsley family (includes Bazel Tinsley, F.H. Tinsley, W.E. Tinsley), 1906-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 17)
    - T (correspondents include H. Tait, Walter S. Tallant, Taylor and Brunton Ore Company, Fred J. Thomas, J.F. Thompson, Fred Thurston, William H. Tibbals, Tonopah Mining Company of Nevada, Joseph B. Toplitz, C.B. Towers, George W. Tucker), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 18)
    - Union Bank and Trust Company (includes George L. Ramsey, Frank Bogart), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 19-20)
    - United States government (includes Assay Office, Bureau of the Census, Forest Service, General Land Office, Geological Survey, Treasury Dept.), 1901-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 21)
    - U-V (correspondents include United States Mining and Power Company, United States Pure Food Company, George Unverzagt, Ellis B. Usher, Valley Forge Mining Company, L.W. VanAkin, P.H. Vanderlick, William Volker and Company), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 22)
    - Washoe Copper Company; Washoe Sampler, 1904-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 23)
    - Tom Watson; Tom Watson Estate, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 24)
    - William K. Weaver, 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 25)
    - H.F. West, Undertaker, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 3 / 26)
    - Western National Bank of the City of New York, 1902-1903 (Box-folder 3 / 27)
    - Ed E. Williams (includes Revenue Mine, Madisonian Mine, Montana Revenue Gold Mining Company), 1904-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 28)
    - W (correspondents include O.F. Wadsworth, Mrs. E.J. Wallace, Andrew J. Walrath, R.B. Wampler, A.J. Warren, David F. Watson, Robert R. Wedekind, Welch and Harrington, J.H. Westerhouse, Western Union Telegraph Company, Henry Wetmore, M.A. White, White Sewing Machine Company, Whitehall State Bank, Mr. & Mrs. Wicks, James Wilkie, John Williams, Lottie Williams, Lewis Wilson, Alvin Womack, Mark W. Woods, Charles F. Word, R. Lee Word), 1902-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 29)
    - Y (correspondents include Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company, Yegen Brothers Savings Bank, W.I Young, unidentified), 1904-1909 (Box-folder 3 / 30)
  - General Correspondence
    - Allen family (includes Charlie E. Allen, Elbert F. Allen, George R. Allen), 1912-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 1)
    - A (correspondents include Louis Abels, Abercrombie and Johnson, Acme Harvesting Machine Company, Army Adams, Julie Albro, Walter Alderson, Almanac Advertising Agency, May Alward, American Bankers Association, American National Bank, American Smelting and Refining Company, Anaconda Copper Mining Company, Charles T. Armstrong, E.F. Armstrong, Mary Glenn Austin, A.H. Averill Machinery Company), 1910-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 2)
    - Bankers... (includes Bankers Insurance Company, Bankers Life Company, Bankers Trust Company), 1910-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 3)
    - B (correspondents include Peter Bacca; Banking Corporation of Montana; Clara E. Barclay; William Barclay; W.S. Bardwell; George A. Beaman; S.L. Bean; Elmer G. Bell; Kate Bell; George Bennett; John G. Bins; Charles E. Black; Jesse S. Bosworth; Eva Bower; I.L. Bower; W.N. Bowman; J.A. Brake; W.H. Brennan; E.M. Brooke; Lisbeth Bromback; Crossland Brooks; Brown, Treacy and Sperry Company; Bryant Supply Company; Robert E. Burns; William J. Burns National Detective Agency; Burroughs Adding Machine Company; William Burtch, Butte Adjustment Company), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 4)
    - W.A. Clark and Brother, 1910-1913 (Box-folder 4 / 5)
    - C (correspondents include William B. Calhoun, Edmund J. Callaway; May H. Carmin, B.J. Carney and Company, E.T. Chapin Company, M.I. Chappell, C.W. Chowning, Mae Church, Citizens' Telephone Company, Clark and Duncan, J.Z. Clem, Conrad Trust and Savings Bank, John S. Cook and Company, Cootey-Blodgett Company, J.A. Copeland, W.H. Copeland), 1910-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 6)
    - Dart Hardware and Implement Company, 1911 (Box-folder 4 / 7)
    - M.M. Duncan (see also Clark and Duncan), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 8-9)
    - D (correspondents include Daly Bank and Trust Company of Butte, W.L. Davis, James S. Dawes, Dayton [Ohio] Chamber of Commerce, A.W. DeGroot, Democratic National Committee, Joseph B. Derbes, W.P. Devereux Company, Nels Distard, E.L. Dodson, Drovers National Bank, V.F. Dusenberry), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 10)
    - Elling family (includes Harrison Elling, Horace B. Elling, Karl Elling, Elling Estate Company, Elling State Bank), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 11)
    - E (correspondents include Economy Power Company; Ely, Salyards and Company; John M. Evans), 1911-1914 (Box-folder 4 / 12)
    - First National Bank of ... (includes Butte, Chicago, Kansas City, Nortonville [Kas], St. Paul, San Francisco, Santa Ana, Three Forks, White Sulphur Springs), 1910-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 13)
    - W.B. Fisher, 1915-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 14)
    - F (correspondents include Benjamin H. Fairbrother, T.J. Farrell Jr., Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis, Emil Felenzer, Louis W. Fenske, F.M. Field, Firemen's Insurance Company, A.S. Fleimer, Mrs. John T. Fletcher, James A. Flint, J.A. Fowler, H.L. Francis, J.S. Freeman), 1910-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 15)
    - R.A. Gillespie, 1914-1915 (Box-folder 4 / 16)
    - P.H. "Harry" Gohn; Virginia Gohn, Henrietta Gohn, 1910-1914 (Box-folder 4 / 17)
    - William Grettum and Company, 1913-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 18)
    - G (correspondents include R.K. Gardner, Garrett and Company, Walter Gatford [?], Sol Genzberger, Grace Virginia Gillham, Elise Girard, Mary Gleim Estate, Goldfield Kewanas Mining Company, Marian E. Goodwin, Gould Grain Company, John Grant, Mrs. R.H. Grey, Gunn-Thompson Company), 1910-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 19)
    - Fayette Harrington, 1912 (Box-folder 4 / 20)
    - E.A. and Samuel Higinbotham, 1912-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 21)
    - J.L. Humphrey (Capital Trust and Savings Bank, Great Falls office), 1916 (Box-folder 4 / 22)
    - H (correspondents include Hadzor Brothers, G.C. Hag, J.E. Hale, George S. Hanson, P.G. Harrington, M.A. Harris, Mrs. H.C. Harrison, Carrie Sleight Hatch, Hawkeye Elevator Company, Mrs. R.N. Hawkins, P.N. Haycraft, Heilbronner Company, Hennepin Mortgage Loan Company, Hilger Loan and Realty Company, Ellen Hiscock, M.J. Hogan, James Hooper, H.L. Hopka, J.E. Howorth, C.W. Hudson, George E. Humiston, Roy L. Hungerford, Hutt and Chesney Mortgage Loan Company), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 23)
    - F.F. and M.M. Irvine, 1910-1915 (Box-folder 4 / 24)
    - I (correspondents include Imperial Hay Company, Cephas Inabnit, Inter-Mountain Brokerage Company, Iron County Bank), 1911-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 25)
    - Jackson (includes E.W. Jackson, John T. Jackson, P.V. Jackson), 1915-1916 (Box-folder 4 / 26)
    - J-K (correspondents include Orson A. Jay, George L. Johns, C.L. Johnson, Arthur D. Jones and Company, Kelly and Kelly, Dema Kennedy, H. Gysbert Klenze, Knapp Company, Roger C. Knox, Berry Knutson, Katie Knutson, Mary Knutson, Alfred S. Kyle, Charles Kyle, Mantie Kyle), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 27)
    - Annie T. Leavitt, 1912-1913 (Box-folder 4 / 28)
    - L (correspondents include A.C. LaRose, Will Lawrence, Levey Brothers and Company, Lewis and Walker, Lydia A. Leyendecker, P.A. Lillis, Lindsay and Company, W.A. Lisheny [?], London Commercial Banking Company, Florence E. Long, Walter A. Lord, Eric Lyngaas), 1910-1917 (Box-folder 4 / 29)